qualitynet.net 2014-12-23

# Privacy Policy | Qualitynet

Share with 

At Qualitynet, your right to privacy and data security is our primary concern that is why we are committed to protecting your privacy when you visit our site. We use the information we collect about you to improve our ability to serve your needs. Below are the guidelines we use for protecting the information you provide us when you visit or use our site. We value the trust that our customers have placed in us. We will protect that trust by respecting the privacy of all our customers, especially as it related to maintaining the confidentiality of any information, which we obtain.

We have prepared this notice to explain what types of customer information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may share it.

Specific types of information for specific purposes:

You can visit our website without giving us any information about yourself.

We have tried our best to minimize the amount of information requested from you. The information we request on this site is required for us to perform the delivery of the service you ordered and when you enter any promotions or surveys.

When you login the first time to your personalized page, we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. For some financial products and services we may also ask for your address, Civil ID/ Passport/ Driving License number and your Credit/ Debit Cards details for completing the transactions. Qualitynet does not store/ save any Credit/ Debit card details into its database or any servers.

Once you register with Qualitynet and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

Qualitynet automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you request.

Qualitynet uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you and conduct researches.

Failure in supplying such data may result in our inability to perform the delivery of the service you ordered.

We do not sell, share or rent the information we collect at this site and we do not use the information for other than internal purposes.

Qualitynet reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to its services, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the Qualitynet Newsletter, that are considered part of your Qualitynet account.

Security Measures:

Qualitynet uses the latest encryption and security technology and fraud detection technique to keep your personal and account information safe and secure.

Although, we will use all reasonable efforts to safeguards the confidentiality of your personal or account information, transmissions made by means of Internet cannot be secure. We will not be liable for disclosures of your information due to errors in transmissions or unauthorized acts of third parties.

Use of Cookies:

When you view the Site, we might store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a â€œCookieâ€ or similar file. Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive, not on our site. Cookies do not spy on you or otherwise invade your privacy, and they cannot invade your hard drive and steal information. Rather, they help you navigate a website as easily as possible. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to prevent you from reentering all your registration data at each connection. Most browsers are set to accept cookies, however, if you prefer, you can set yours to refuse them.

Non-Disclosure of Personal Information to Outside Parties:

Qualitynet does not share, sell or rent its customer´s information to anyone. We take your trust very seriously.

Links to third party websites

When you click on links that take you to third party websites, you will be subject to the third parties Privacy Policies.

While we support the protection of privacy on the Internet, Qualitynet cannot be responsible for the actions of third parties. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement whenever interacting with any website.

Update or Change of Personal information:

If at any time, you would like to change, amend or update any personal information in your account, just go to the My Account link under Member´s Area (your personalized page). Here you can change your login password and or update other personal information.

Use of IP Addresses

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, any fraud or abuse of the services, and to administer our website.

Right of Access and Correction

Qualitynet may revise this Privacy and Security policy at any time, effective upon posting the revised Terms and Conditions on the Site. Continue access or use by User of the Site after posting of the revisions by Qualitynet, shall constitute User´s acceptance and agreement to the changes in the Terms and Conditions.

Respect of Customer’s Privacy

Your trust is important to us. We are committed to protecting your privacy, whether you do business with us in person, online, by telephone or mail. Our aim is to continue to provide our customers with services, with the highest standards of quality and maximum customer benefits. We look forward to serving you.

Contacting us

Should you have any questions about this Privacy and Security Policy, its practices or your dealings with Qualitynet´s website, you can contact us at the following addresses:

**Customer support:**  
**Tel:** **1804444**  
**Fax: 22413782**  
**Support E-mail:** [**support@qualitynet.net**](mailto:support@qualitynet.net)
